humanconnectome.org 2017-06-13

# Privacy Statement | Human Connectome Project

The member universities of the Human Connectome Project take privacy very seriously, whether dealing with participant data or the data of those visiting this website. 

The participant data from our research into the Human Connectome that is stored in our XNAT server is de-identified, and contains no personal health information (PHI). 

Our website collects names and email addresses via our contact form. This information is used solely by the administrators and members of the HCP website and is not shared, traded or sold to third parties under any circumstances. 

Our website may also collect non-personal data about site visits, sessions, and IP addresses. This information is only used for diagnostic or debugging purposes, to help us optimize our website's performance, and is not shared externally. This is a standard practice for most websites, and this data is never linked with personally identifiable information. 

This website contains links to other websites, whose content we think is relevant. However, the HCP website is not responsible for maintaining or updating the content of these other sites. If any of these sites are found to contain irrelevant or offensive information, please contact us. 

By using humanconnectome.org, you signify your agreement to our privacy policy as stated above. Note that this policy may be revised periodically without notice. Please re-read this policy prior to submitting any personal information if you have concerns about how your information is being collected and used.
